The purest form of war is one on one.
Killing Season is a action, thriller film directed by Mark Steven Johnson.
Two veterans of the Bosnian War, one American, one Serbian,
clash in the remote Smoky Mountain wilderness.
Benjamin Ford, played by Robert De Niro.
Emil Kovac, played by John Travolta.
Chris Ford, played by Milo Ventimiglia.
Sarah Ford, played by Liz Olin.
Elena, played by Diana Lyubenova.
Serbian, played by Kalin Sarmenov.
Killing Season is a 2013 American action thriller film written by Evan Daugherty and directed by Mark Steven
Johnson for Millennium Films, as the first on-screen pairing of John Travolta and Robert De Niro.
The film pertains to a personal fight between an
American and a Serb war veteran.
Daugherty's script caught the attention of producers after winning
the 2008 Script Pipeline Screenwriting Competition.
The film received negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of hunter, bosnia and
herzegovina, gore, baptism, revenge.
The tone is intense.